https://www.natural-source.com/us/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

You can now find all our products on our NEW website! www.maisonbeljanski.com
Not sure what to buy? Contact us and get advice from a Healthcare Professional
Shipping To :
Call us at
+1 212 308 7066 (M-F 9am-6pm EST)
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy sets out how EVI Liberty Corporation, hereafter referred to as "Maison Beljanski," uses and protects the information you provide when you are using this website. The personal data of customers, prospects and visitors to the Maison Beljanski website are secure and treated with the utmost care. When asked to provide certain information to identify you while using this site, please be assured that it will be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Collector
The personal data collected as part of the activities of the website are processed by:Evi Liberty Corp. ("Maison Beljanski")317 EAST 53RD STREETNEW YORK, NY 10022 UNITED STATES OF AMERICA
Personal data we collect
What data?
We collect and process your name, address, email address, password, phone number, IP address, connection data, navigation data, order history, and preferences. The mandatory or optional nature of the data is reported to you during collection by an asterisk. Some data is collected automatically because of your actions on the site. We also measure audience, for example the number of page views, the number of visits to the site, as well as the activity of visitors to the site and their frequency of return. Maison Beljanski uses this data to sells its products and services and to inform customers and website visitors of the activities, products and services it offers.
When?
We collect the information that you provide us, especially when:
you create your account "My account"
you place an order on our website
you browse our site and consult products
you contact our Customer Service
you write a comment
How we use your personal data
Management of your order
Information and data about you are necessary for the management of your orders and our commercial relations. This information may also be kept for evidence in compliance with legal and regulatory obligations (payment, litigation ...)
Payments with bank data retention
For the purposes of payments made to Maison Beljanski, your bank details are collected and kept by our payment service provider certified PCI-DSS. This standard is an international security standard whose objectives are to ensure the confidentiality and integrity of cardholder data, and thus secure the protection of card and transaction data. Your bank details are securely stored for the time needed to make payments for the products and services you order on this website, as well as for refund and guarantee transactions and treatments. You can link your credit cards to your account to facilitate your future purchases. If you delete a card registered in your account, your bank details will no longer appear in your online account or in future orders, but they will be kept by our payment service provider within the limits required to process payments for the purposes of your orders and their consequences (payment, after-sales, operations, litigation ...)
Our Newsletters
If you have registered to receive our newsletters, you can receive offers by electronic communication (emails) to keep you informed of our news and offers that can benefit you. We measure the opening rate of our electronic mailings in order to adapt them to your needs. If you no longer wish to receive our offers and information, you can update your preferences at any time by changing it in “My account”, or by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the email or by stating it by mail.
Comments
Any comments, will have to be reviewed and approved before posting. Maison Beljanski reserves the right to oppose a hypertext link that would be contrary to its interests and violate its rights. Maison Beljanski may or in this case require the holder of this comment to delete the link. If the holder refuses, Maison Beljanski reserves the right to defend its interests by any means of law.
Sharing Data
Sharing data with third parties
Certain data concerning you is transmitted to our partners for delivery of your orders. We share only what is necessary to insure a smooth delivery of you order.
Social Networks
In order to give you the opportunity to share content or give your opinion on our products or services, we may have to integrate into our site elements (buttons, plug-ins, ...) in connection with social networks. These elements allow social networks to follow your navigation, provided that you are connected to the social network on your browser (even if there was no use of the "share" button, for example). The conditions of use of information related to these elements are defined by the social network of which you are a member, we have no control over the actions performed. We invite you to consult the privacy policies of these social networks to learn about the use of the data collected during your browsing and how to set the confidentiality of your accounts.
Your rights as a data subject
In general, in accordance with US privacy policy and European data protection regulations (GDPR), you have the right to access and right of rectification and deletion of your data. You may also object for a legitimate reason to the use of your data, or without having to justify a reason when your right of opposition aims to stop any responsibility of Maison Beljanski. Finally, you can define guidelines for the retention, deletion and communication of your personal data after your death. To exercise your rights, simply write to us online at info@natural-source.com or by mail: EVI LIBERTY, CORP. ("MAISON BELJANSK")317 EAST 53RD STREETNEW YORK, NY 10022 UNITED STATES OF AMERICA
by indicating to us your first name, last name, and email address. In accordance with the regulations in force, any request for the exercise of your rights must be signed and accompanied by a photocopy of an identity document bearing your signature and specify the address to which the reply must be sent to you. An answer will be sent to you within 2 months of receiving the request.
Security and Confidentiality
Maison Beljanski makes every reasonable effort to ensure the security of transactions that occur on the websites. To maintain data accuracy, prevent unauthorized access, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put appropriate physical, electronic, and administrative procedures in place to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We utilize SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology, which encrypts our visitors' credit card numbers, names, and addresses. This site is also a Rapid SSL secure site and PCI DSS (Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard) compliant, which ensures security and protection of sensitive customer credit card information.
Cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your need,likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. Doing so may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
Associated with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores category info on the page, that allows pages to display more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency.
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer ID with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID.
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer has allowed the use of cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites, and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. Please exercise caution and view the privacy statements applicable to the website in question.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
Maison Beljanski may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
2.5.0.0
Login
Remember Me
Register
Login
Forgot password?
Select Your Profile
Next
Forgot Your Password?
Please enter your email address below. You will receive a link to reset your password.
*Email Address
Back
Submit
Please select the country where you wish your package to be shipped.
For your convenience we have preselected your country and language based on your browser. However you may change it if it does not correspond to your shipping address.
SHIPPING COUNTRY
AfghanistanÅland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo - BrazzavilleCongo - KinshasaCook IslandsCosta RicaCôte d’IvoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard & McDonald IslandsHondurasHong Kong SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacau SAR ChinaMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmar (Burma)NamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorth KoreaNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoriesPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandsPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRéunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSamoaSan MarinoSão Tomé and PríncipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia & South Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSt. Vincent & GrenadinesSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayU.S. Outlying IslandsU.S. Virgin IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezuelaVietnamWallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweUnited States
Currency :
LANGUAGE
English
French
